Okay, so what you're about to see here is Tennessee's speaker, Cameron Sexton, shove
Representative Justin J. Pearson. Now, I don't know if he thinks Pearson is a sucker. I don't
know if he thought that was okay. But I will tell you, don't ever count the brother with the afro
and the dashiki out. That man is doing martial arts. What these brothers, Justin J. Pearson,
Justin Jones, and anybody really who's of sound mind are having to deal with in Tennessee
is a very, very serious issue. And I think a lot of us don't necessarily take it seriously,
but what we're watching is an actual overtaking of government. And we have seen that this turns
violent. We have seen that this turns personal. And I hope that these brothers are being protected.
There's one thing white people in power don't like is when black people have the nerve to think that
they have power too.